SPECIAL NEW YEAR'S MESSAGE - PROPHET T.B. JOSHUA
Viewers all over the world, there are many activities in this season.
Some celebrate this way, others that way
but we are here as children of God, born of God,
to celebrate in His presence.
In His presence, we are strong. Glory be to God.
Our message this season – 'Offence'.
Offence is the effective instrument used by satan to trap us,
to imprison us and make us bondservants.
We are here today to celebrate our Lord, Jesus. It's all about Jesus.
Just because you were mistreated,
just because you were wrongly accused or lied against,
you do not have permission or right to hold onto offence.
As we all know, offence is a trap of the enemy.
We are usually shocked, surprised and bewildered when offended,
as if we are the only one wronged.
Jesus made it abundantly clear:
It is impossible to live among people, to live this life
and not have the opportunity to be offended.
I mean, it is impossible that no offence should come.
It is not a question of opportunity to be offended but what your response will be.
Remember, our response determines our future.
Your response determines your future.
When I'm hurt, my response determines my future.
Expectation of certain behaviours from our dear ones sets us up for offence.
For instance, I'm expecting you to greet me
because I helped you and you ignore me.
This is one of the roots of offence.
This New Year, my brothers and sisters, expectation of certain behaviours
should carefully be observed.
I'm expecting this from you; I'm expecting that from you.
There is nothing bad about that but this should not lead to offence.
I want to greet you once again, Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
Viewers all over the world, the Lord said I should pray with you
after delivering the message and I want to pray with you.
Offence is the effective instrument used by satan to imprison us,
to entrap us and make us one of his own.
I want to pray with you.
Whatever caused by offence -
envy, jealousy, outrage, strifes, resentment, pain, hurts, deep hurts -
end with this year, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever caused by offence -
pain of the past, hatred, bitterness, envy, jealousy, isolation, depression -
end with this year, in the name of Jesus!
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be free from whatever caused by offence!
I say, you are free, in the name of Jesus!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Lord. In Jesus Christ's name. Amen.
I have a couple of things to introduce to you.
This is one of the blessings God has inspired me to give to you -
'Believer's Card'.
My prayer partner.
Your prayer partner – T.B. Joshua. I am your prayer partner.
This is a blessing for you with a seal of authentic authorisation.
I want to identify with you. We want to rededicate ourselves, our relationship,
and to let you know that I know you - you know me. Yes.
Viewers, thank you very much.
We want to prepare you in reading the prophecy for the year.
We have 3 parts, and I am going to read part 1.
Remaining parts 2 and 3 we leave for the next Sunday, or other Sunday.
Right now, I want to read the first part of the prophecy -
what you should expect next year.
I have to read it; it's an instruction from God.
It's purely Heaven; Heaven knows about this.
It came to me, I received it and the Lord said I should give you.
This is the Word of God.
SPECIAL NEW YEAR'S MESSAGE - PROPHET T.B. JOSHUA
Viewers all over the world, before we start prayer,
I have with me the prophecy for the New Year.
There will be large scale scarcity, shortage of food.
As a state, country, continent, we have to go back to the farm to arrest the forthcoming situation.
Number 2:
Some countries will suffer excessive rainfall while others will suffer drought.
That means that some countries will have no rain, and if there is rain, it comes at the wrong time.
This is a prophecy for the whole world.
I encourage the governments of all nations to invest in agriculture
and to grant loans to deserving citizens to enhance this effort.
The continent of Africa – how much we have disappointed God.
Africa is supposed to be the breadbasket of the world.
We are supposed to produce a large sum of food for the whole world.
This is our natural resource base.
Food should be our primary export to other continents -
food in exchange for technology.
Let's go back to where we are coming from.
Let's go back to the promise of God we have abandoned.
Let's go back to our destiny.
Politics – African leaders should quickly arrest the political situation that is coming.
More African countries will be under siege by terrorists
because of pros and cons, for and against, in choosing leaders in their countries.
Mishandling of electoral processes will create a conducive atmosphere for terrorists.
Politics will not be business as usual because of limited resources.
There will be no profit in investing in politics
because of governments' limited resources and challenges.
This now gives grace to those who are genuinely called to the job.
When you are genuinely called to the job,
you will do it because of your love for it and not because of money.
This year, do what you love.
There is money in love.
Money in love brings peace and tranquillity.
Back to my country Nigeria and my president, President Buhari.
He has good intentions.
A king's intentions cannot be carried out properly without the support of the subjects.
He needs your support to lead us out of the valley.
We are in the valley.
Nigeria - we are in the valley.
I am not saying "valley of shadow of death" but I say "we are in the valley".
It is not our President who put us in the valley, it is a generational issue.
We have gradually been going into the valley.
The reality of that valley has come. We have seen, we are in the valley.
My country Nigeria – the president will do everything to reject revaluation of the naira,
which is a good idea from a good leader.
But there will be overwhelming pressure which he will not be able to resist.
No one can resist it.
As far as he is a human being, he will not be able to resist it.
There will be an overwhelming pressure from above him.
He will not be able to resist.
No one is to be blamed. Everyone has a portion to be blamed for.
If you are from Nigeria, you are to be blamed.
Let us share the blame and move the country forward.
Nigerians, let us support and pray for our leaders.
The future of this country is crying for help.
We are in the valley.
I am not saying "valley of shadow of death" - take note of that. Press men, for your information:
please quote me well. Thank you.
Being in a valley is different from being in a valley of shadow of death.
Valley means - there is a hill here.
There is a hill here; there is hill there.
But you are now trapped from coming out.
When you say "valley of shadow of death", you mean there is snake, python, lion, crocodile,
with you in the valley but our case is not like that.
We are in the valley but there is no crocodile, no lion, no tiger there.
We are just alone there.
But it is also very difficult because if you are in the valley, there is no food, no money.
Therefore, let us support our leaders, our president and pray for him.
We should pray for a North Korean leader this time.
But I'm not going to go into that because it is time to pray now.
Yes. My brothers and sisters, start your year on your knees.
Tell your neighbour, "Start your year on your knees".
SPECIAL NEW YEAR'S MESSAGE - PROPHET T.B. JOSHUA
Viewers all over the world, right now, start your year on your knees.
Start your year on your knees.
Let us thank God for giving us a new beginning.
I give You glory and honour over my people, nation and the world.
Glory be to God for giving us a new beginning.
Viewers all over the world, what you were destined to become, this is the year to become it.
Give thanks to God because this is the year of reward.
No matter the difficulty or trouble, our troubles make us stronger.
This is the year of reward.
What you are destined to become, this is the year to become it.
Right now, give thanks to God.
Yes. Your struggle will make you stronger. Give thanks to Him.
I decree this, in the name of Jesus.
What you were destined to become, this is the year to become it, in the name of Jesus!
This is the year to become it, in the name of Jesus!
Once again, listen to me.
What you were destined to become, this is the year to become it, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
The voice of weeping shall be silent, in the name of Jesus!
The voice of difficulty, sorrow and setback shall be silent!
There shall no longer be weeping, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I decree this, in the name of Jesus.
Be rescued, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever unfavourable situation you are in, I prophesy it ends with this year!
Be it your business, health or family – it ends with this year, in the name of Jesus!
It ends with this year, in the name of Jesus!
Once again, note – whatever unfavourable situation -
your situation could be a financial situation, business or family -
whatever your health challenges or unfavourable...
I am not praying for you; I am prophesying.
I am telling you the mind of God.
Those of you that are under the influence of my voice right now,
under the influence of this telecast at this moment, start your year on your knees.
Right now, whatever unfavourable situation you are in, it ends with this year, in the name of Jesus.
Let there be light!
Let there be light in your way, business, career, health and family!
Once again, whatever unfavourable situation you are in, by the authority in the name of Jesus,
I prophesy, it ends with this year, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Be free! Be rescued!
Start a new beginning -
a new beginning in your way,
a new beginning in your business,
a new beginning in your finances,
a new beginning in your health,
a new beginning in your family!
A new beginning!
It has been decreed – a new beginning.
This year is a year of reward.
Yes. As a Christian, God is our Rewarder.
You believers, God is your Rewarder.
As you lay your bed, you lie on it.
This is time for you to reconcile your way with the Lord.
In order for you to have Jesus Christ, you must let go of offence.
Let go of all hurt. Deep hurt – let go.
Bitterness, outrage, strifes, hatred, jealousy caused by offence - let go of offence, in the name of Jesus.
Continue to live under His protection
and dwell in His shadow the rest of your life.
In Jesus Christ's name I pray. Amen.
When you wake up in the morning, go on your knees.
Mean it with all your heart.
Go on your knees; ask for His mercy and favour every day.
This is the instruction from God.
Go on your knees when you are about to sleep.
You wake up in the morning, go on your knees and say,
"Lord Jesus, Your favour and mercy are all I need".
Now, God has given you a new beginning and I am here too to prophesy and tell you that
every unfavourable situation you are in - it ends with this year, the year 2015.
Emmanuel. Thank You, Lord. In Jesus' name. Amen.
Thank You, Lord. Father, we thank You.
Son of David, we thank You for Your mercy and favour upon Your children.
You have given them instruction.
Give them a hearing heart to obey Your Word.
Father, give them the grace to continue to live under Your protection
and dwell in Your shadow the rest of their lives, in Jesus' name. Amen.
Thank You, Lord.
2016 YEAR OF REWARD
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of all Nations.
Emmanuel TV – Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.